And like oh we've
caught so many crabs
What are we going
to do now We're
like okay well let's
just take it back
to the Okay great
idea 15 year old
Kylie So we go
back to this hotel
and we're like yeah
now we brought the
crabs back to What
do we do We're
like okay let's just
put it in a
Okay let's put the
in a That night
every crab started
breaking each other apart
They killed each other
in that tub Such
a dark story okay
It is the most
gruesome thing I've done
at 15 I'm like
and then we were
like hey let's get
them out Let's put
them back on the
beach Like what the
heck's going on it's
just they kill each
other in that tub
And I was really
sad right I mean
maybe that's why I've
been a vegan for
nine years I don't
know right But it's
like it was just
like horrible to watch
And I always wonder
like why did the
kill each other So
I think that like
I just don't want
us to each other
Okay You we're in
a bucket right now
We're in this tub
And like it's not
like new water new
nutrients It's not like
an abundant ocean our
echo chamber or whatever
We're in this echo
chamber tub don't want
I like like this
beach with this And
you know like I'm
not to kill another
crab because like I
have other things to
do I've got like
I need a hunt
for food I need
to procreate you know
Cause there's this abundance
of this